[SUNG JINWOO] The purified
blood of the demon monarch.
I finally have
all the ingredients.
♪
[gasps]
The success rate and quantity
depend on my intellect stats?
Is everything all right,
Sir Jinwoo?
[sighs]
Craft it.
♪
[gasps]
[sighs]
[SUNG JINWOO]
The Elixir of Life.
This is it.
The thing that will cure Mom.
At least...
I hope.
-[rumbling]
-Uh?
Ah?
[thudding]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Oh, Iron.
[chuckles]
Thanks, buddy!
Arise.
♪
[gasps]
Hm?
[SUNG JINWOO]
A name. Uh, right.
Um, what was it?
Kaise... No, Karka something?
[clicks tongue]
[sighs]
[ESIL] Remembering names isn't
really your strong suit, is it?
[SUNG JINWOO]
Whatever.
I'mma call you...Kaisel.
[roars]
[ESIL]
He can fly us home in no time!
I just know Father
will be thrilled
and want to hold a grand
celebration at the castle!
Huh?
Sir Jinwoo?
[SUNG JINWOO]
I've gotta get back
-as soon as possible...
-Hello?!
-...to test the Elixir.
-Are you listening to me?
Wait, I should have
a new rune stone.
-[ESIL] A fun, lavish party!
-[SUNG JINWOO] Not those.
[SUNG JINWOO]
Not that, either.
C'mon, let's see.
Ah, here we go.
♪
Shadow Exchange.
Oh, nice!
So that means
I can switch places
with any of my shadow soldiers?
I like that.
Hm?
[SUNG JINWOO]
Sorry, Esil, but you'll need
to head back on your own.
[ESIL] What about the fun,
lavish party?
[SUNG JINWOO]
Ah, the Radish manor's
on the 80th floor.
That's a bit
outta the way for me.
[ESIL]
It is?
Let's meet again
if fate allows it.
-Take care, okay.
-[gasps]
I have one last thing to say!
[gasps]
Ah!
[sighs]
♪
[SUNG JINWOO] This is where
he was patrolling.
We really switched.
Hmm.
It's got a three hour
cooldown time,
but I'm not about to walk, so!
[grunts]
Kaisel!
[electricity crackling]
[roars]
[GO GUNHEE] The Japanese
hunters will act as bait.
Once the ants are drawn out,
we'll use a special signal
to disrupt their hive mind.
Then we'll send a detachment
of hunters into the colony
while it's vulnerable.
They'll take out
whatever's left
and kill the queen.
Only question is
whether or not the signal
will function the way
it should.
[Go Gunhee sighs]
Yes, I can't deny I have doubts
about this strategy.
[sighs]
However, our analysts
signed off on it,
and it make sense on paper.
In the event
the signal should fail,
withdrawal was also included
as a contingency plan.
♪
All we can do now
is prepare our team.
When it comes time to act,
our hunters
will be ready for anything.
Right.
[GO GUNHEE]
On that note...
were you able
to reach Hunter Sung?
[WOO JINCHUL]
No, not yet, sir.
[groans]
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
Yoonho, c'mon!
Getting drinks
should be relaxing,
but you can't even
crack a smile?
I know how funny
that story I just told you is.
[gulps]
Sorry, guess I missed
the punchline.
Well, frowning's only gonna
give you wrinkles, man.
-What the hell does that mean?
-[laughs]
[BAEK YOONHO] Hard not to envy
a guy like Byung-gu.
You don't meet
many S-rank healers,
let alone ones
who retired so young
with all their limbs and their
sense of humor intact.
[sighs]
But as his former comrade,
I'm happy he's still
in such good spirits.
Ah, thanks.
-[MIN BYUNG-GU] Yoonho.
-Hm?
Are you really gonna
go back there?
I am.
Even after seeing the way
Eunseok went out?
♪
[sighs]
[BAEK YOONHO]
Especially after that.
If we don't put a stop
to these flying ants,
they'll infest the whole
country and more will die.
Funny, since you've
never struck me
as a patriot until now.
Well, I'm going either way,
but I thought
a noble-sounding excuse would
make people think I'm cool.
[gulps]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
I guess he did tell us
the same thing,
or something close.
[sighs]
I know they need
S-ranks, but I'm retired.
So, if you were gonna
try to convince me--
[BAEK YOONHO] Look,
I just wanted to say goodbye,
since I might not
ever see you again.
♪
[MIN BYUNG-GU] I'm, uh,
taking the civil service exam.
Then, you aren't retired.
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
I am, from the battlefield.
It's just too much for me.
Hmm.
So, I'll get a government job.
The history part's
gonna be cake.
Not sure about the rest.
You always were a history buff.
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
Have I ever told you
why I love period dramas
so much?
Enlighten me.
Because...
they're all in the past.
And if you ask me, that's
the only place war belongs.
Fair enough,
can't argue that.
[BAEK YOONHO] Any normal person
would say the same.
But hunters aren't normal.
Don't think I've met one
who doesn't like fighting
apart from Byung-gu.
Combat becomes routine.
We almost have to enjoy it.
Hmm.
[BAEK YOONHO] Maybe that trait
is a condition for awakening.
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
Yoonho, your forehead!
You're trying to get wrinkles,
aren't you?
[BAEK YOONHO] Uh!
Shut up and drink!
You indulge
like a college boy, though.
Ah!
[chuckles]
[BAEK YOONHO]
Indulge this, jackass.
[machine beeping]
[metal clattering]
[Sung Jinwoo trembling]
[gasps]
[sighs]
[sobbing]
[SUNG JINWOO] She got
those burns because of me.
[sighs]
[machine beeping]
She might not be
able to swallow it.
And even if she does,
there are no guarantees.
But...I've seen
the kind of miracles
the system is capable of.
It brought me from an E-rank
to where I am now.
[machine beeping]
[deep inhales]
I need to have faith.
[machine beeping]
[footfall]
[deep breath]
♪
[sighs]
[gasps]
Hm.
Mom.
♪
Come on,
you've gotta wake up!
Everything I've gone through
to get stronger,
it was all for you.
[deep breath]
Open your eyes, Mom.
[whimpering]
Please.
♪
[sighs]
[inhales]
What is going on with me?
I can't seem
to focus at all today.
[vehicle passing]
[deep breath]
[wind rustling]
[SUNG JINAH]
That warm breeze feels nice.
♪
[curtains rustling]
[gasps]
[sighs]
Hey...
sweet boy.
[Sung Jinwoo whimpering]
[PARK KYUNG-HYE]
How long have I been asleep?
Four...
Four years.
And Jinah?
[sniffles]
She's doing really well.
[gasps]
Then you're both okay.
[PARK KYUNG-HYE] Thank you
for keeping your promise.
♪
Look at how much
you've grown up,
you're covered
in scrapes and bruises.
Baby, you must've been through
so much this whole time.
[whimpering]
I am so proud of you.
♪
-[crying]
-[PARK KYUNG-HYE] Hey, hey.
I'm okay.
[crying]
[weeping]
♪
I'm okay.
You've done so well...
Jinwoo.
[crying]
♪
[sobbing]
[HEAD DOCTOR 21A]
She awoke from Eternal Sleep?
[DOCTOR 21A] As hard
as it is to believe, yes.
Her family has requested
immediate release,
and seeing as all of her vitals
are functioning normally,
I have no reason to deny them.
♪
[whimpering]
You're beautiful.
Jinah.
[sobbing]
You're okay!
[PARK KYUNG-HYE]
I'm sorry I worried you.
[Sung Jinah sobbing]
[SUNG JINWOO] [chuckles]
It was all worth it.
This...is the reward
I wanted the whole time.
[camera shutter clicking]
First, thank you for coming
and providing coverage
on this matter.
As you're aware,
the giant ants from Jeju
are now capable of flight,
and have even escaped
the island,
leaving death
and devastation in their wake.
It cannot continue.
Thus, on behalf
of the Hunter's Association,
I'm announcing our fourth raid
to contain the Jeju Island
dungeon break.
This time,
we won't just be relying
on our own country's strength.
We'll have the prowess and
support of ten S-rank hunters
from Japan as well.
But this isn't a purely
S-rank operation
by any means.
We want to ensure
the safety of the public.
So, A-ranks and below
will protect the waters
and the mainland.
♪
Our plan is set, and we will
see it through to the end.
[camera shutter clicking]
Hmm.
[snoring]
[MIN BYUNG-GU]
Honestly, Eunseok.
I'm straight terrified
of this upcoming raid.
Yeah, I'm pretty
scared too, man.
But, the ones
who can't defend themselves
must be hundreds of times
more afraid than us.
So, let's end it.
For the people who don't have
the means to or the choice.
We can't sit by
while our country turns
into an anthill, now can we?
[BAEK YOONHO]
You bastards!
I'm gonna stomp
out your little nest.
[sighs]
Everything about
this guy is unpredictable.
From powers to personality.
[snoring]
[EUNSEOK] Not many
could help someone like him
when he needs it...
but you and I can.
[sighs]
[Sung Jinah awkward laughs]
[clattering]
Sis, I only left you alone
for one week.
Now, now...
I have four years of housework
to make up for anyway.
And we've got
six hands between us.
[machine whirring]
No denying this place
is showing its age, huh.
Some of these older stains
just won't come out.
It's no surprise.
We've lived
in this same apartment
since I was born.
I suppose that's true.
[SUNG JINWOO]
I've wanted this for so long...
[PARK KYUNG-HYE] Depends
on what's in the fridge.
[SUNG JINWOO]
...and yet, I feel so anxious.
[SUNG JINAH]...together in
four years, so let's eat out!
[SUNG JINWOO]
Since the reawakening.
I've crossed a line I don't
think I can come back from.
-[PARK KYUNG-HYE] Jinwoo.
-Uh?
[SUNG JINWOO]
Yes, Mom?
[sighs]
[PARK KYUNG-HYE] Has there been
any word from your father?
[Sung Jinah sighs]
Hm.
[PARK KYUNG-HYE]
I saw you became a hunter, too.
You're all over the news.
Yeah.
Actually, do you remember
when your father
was a firefighter?
The way he always wanted
to help people
might be the biggest reason
I became his wife.
And it looks like you've
inherited that part of him.
[chuckles]
Hey, do you think
my dream of being a doctor
is 'cause of Dad, too?
[PARK KYUNG-HYE]
Yes, you're both
your father's children,
no doubt.
[SUNG JINAH]
Yeah, we're pretty great.
-[phone vibrating]
-[Sung Jinah laughs]
Hello?
[sighs]
[WOO JINCHUL] Good work
with the press conference, sir.
Thank you.
And thank you
for all of your assistance.
[WOO JINCHUL]
Of course.
I was glad
that you were present
for our unexpected
guest's visit.
♪
[WOO JINCHUL]
Yes, Thomas Andre.
An American S-rank
with enough power
to rival a whole country.
It was my hope he was here
to join the mission.
[GO GUNHEE] The timing
did make it seem that way.
But someone strong enough
to take on national militaries
is literally a one-man army.
He can't casually intervene
in foreign affairs.
[WOO JINCHUL]
True.
But then why'd he come
if not to help?
Could be he meant what he said.
He did tell us he'd pop in
when he was around.
Perhaps he came to warn us
about Hunter Hwang's
intentions.
Or maybe, it was
for something else entirely.
[sighs]
Any luck getting in contact
with Hunter Sung yet?
[WOO JINCHUL]
Yes, just a moment ago.
He'll be here shortly.
[footfall]
[GO GUNHEE]
We strike in four days.
It's a raid we've been
wanting to launch for years.
Would you be willing
to lend us your strength?
[sighs]
[SUNG JINWOO] It's a perfect
opportunity to level up.
I'd hate to let it go.
Or...I would've hated to.
[inhales]
-Well, sir...
-[rumbling]
[SUNG JINWOO]
Uh?
Magic power?
[Go Gunhee laughs]
They're pretty far away.
I'm impressed
you could sense that.
There's no cause
for alarm, though.
Our S-ranks are just
getting a little exercise.
If you're curious...
we can go take a look.
♪
[growling]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[grunts]
Say, Master Baek.
Might wanna stop
skipping leg day.
Gotta train your lower body
while you're young!
I would, if I could do burpees
at my desk, Master Ma!
[growls]
[GO GUNHEE]
It's rare, indeed.
For all these S-ranks
to gather in one place.
I'd guess that wave
of power you felt
was most likely a result
of these two sparring.
Hunter Baek is being pushed
pretty hard, isn't he?
Because he hasn't exactly
gotten serious yet.
Hunter Ma would feel
the strain otherwise.
If you weren't aware,
the robust fellow
in the white gi is Dongwook Ma
of the Fame Guild.
[cackles]
But why is he
holding back at all?
Doesn't seem like
Hunter Ma is a guy
you should do that with.
Yes, well, Yoonho
can't really cut loose
when he's fighting humans.
If he unleashed his full power,
he'd turn into a monster.
[SUNG JINWOO] I have heard
rumors he transforms in battle.
Over there,
next to Hunters Cha and Lim,
we have some members
of the Knights Guild.
Ah, and here come our guests.
♪
The S-rank hunters from Japan,
including their guild master,
Ryuji Goto.
[SHIMIZU AKARI]
Ah!
Hey, who's that guy?
That is Hunter Jinwoo Sung.
He was named S-rank
very recently.
He's a strong
assassin type, right?
No.
I'm almost certain
that he's a mage, sir.
[GOTO RYUJI]
Him?
Hey, if it isn't the guy
who ruined
Minsung's publicity stunt
just by opting
to go through the front door.
-[gasps]
-[GO GUNHEE] I know.
[CHA HAE-IN] No wonder
I felt the air in here shift.
[growls]
[laughs]
[HANEKAWA] If this is the best
their country has to offer,
I'm a bit disappointed.
I suppose watching your fights
has spoiled me somewhat.
Other S-ranks
simply can't compare.
I don't know if I agree.
[PARK JONGSOO]
Miss interpreter lady.
I ain't entirely sure
what you said
but I caught
your disgusted tone.
Sounded like
you were mockin' us.
You're amazing, Mister Park!
And you are?
You're lookin'
at the reputable guild master
of the Knights Guild,
Mister Jongsoo Park himself!
Jongsoo Park?
Can't say I've ever
heard that name.
Uh...well, you might
not've heard of him before
on account of him bein'
an A-rank instead of an S.
But we're still one of the five
biggest guilds in the country!
We'll be actin'
as security on this--
[LIM TAE-GYU]
Having fun over here?
If you're thinking
of causing a scene,
I suggest that you not.
[PARK JONGSOO]
These folks were sayin'
we're a buncha weaklings,
so they're the cause of this!
[LIM TAE-GYU]
Doesn't matter. Chill out.
[speaking in Japanese]
[HANEKAWA] We have
a rare chance to spar together.
All these S-ranks in one room.
[sighs]
A-ranks not good enough for ya?
Feel free
to set your own rules,
but let's keep it friendly.
[GO GUNHEE]
Well, I'm on board.
Although, let's exclude any
mage types or noncombatants
since it's difficult for them
to compete alone.
That's fine with me.
All right, then we're all
agreed it's combat types only.
If someone grabs your wrist,
you get tagged on the back,
or anything besides your feet
hits the floor, you're done.
You automatically lose.
And instead
of one-on-one matches,
we'll do a free-for-all.
[PARK JONGSOO]
Why?
[BAEK YOONHO] 'Cause the raid
we're preparing for
is bound to be just as chaotic.
[smirks]
[sighs]
Sounds fair enough.
Let's go with that.
♪
[GO GUNHEE] The representatives
for our team will be
Hunters Cha, Lim,
Ma, and Baek.
[GOTO RYUJI] And our team
will be Hunters Tawata,
Kumamoto, Hoshino,
and Tanaka.
♪
[GO GUNHEE] Now then,
if everyone's ready,
let the free-for-all...begin.
♪